Thanks for looking:)
Mmm
uh-huh
uh
Good afternoon.
Hello.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll turn it.
Was it spinning?
Very much.
I sang something about Southern music.
You were singing.
You know...
Today?
Yes...
I've invited a guest.
I'd like you to have a private talk with him.
I don't know...
Koyama-san...
I only heard that he and Ms. Koyama are going to meet.
I just heard that he's going to meet her.
You know...
I've never talked to her.
Almost.
Almost never.
We've never really talked.
Really.
I don't even know why I thought we'd meet.
I hope we meet.
I'm sure we will.Yes, it is.
So, since this is really our first time alone together.
I've prepared some topics for you to talk about.
Yes, sir.
The theme is the only thing that's decided.
This one?
Yes.
That's it.
I'll call you when I have 10 minutes.
We'll talk when you get here.
Yes, sir.
Please do.
Oh! Are you there?
Yes, sir.
Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
That's funny.
That's your seat.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Thank you.
You're not cold?
I'm fine.
Are you okay?
Let me get you a drink.
Sure, let's have a drink.
This is the best menu here.
It's all on the menu.All the menu items at a glance
I'll have a hot one.
A latte? Do you have a latte?
Yeah, a latte.
Yeah, sure.
You'll order it for me?
I'll order it.
I feel like I'm being bullied.
A latte? Hot latte?
No latte. I'll have a latte.
Hot cafe au lait.
Yes, um, Nicole.
Why did you say your name?
She wants a hot café, so I'll have a hot café.
What about you, Aro?
I'll have orange juice.
100%.
One hundred percent.
You definitely don't have to tell me your name, karaoke.
At the karaoke bar.
Okay. - Okay.
I'm, uh... I'm nervous.
What are you going to say?
Mr. Oyasama wants to get you two in a room.
He said he wants to put them in a hole.
He said that?
You don't like it?
No, I'm so happy.
We've never talked before, you know.I've never spoken to you, you know, properly.
There were two or three times in the variety
Longha's Sports Day and
Longha.
Just Longhorns.
Yes, I have.
So it's not solid.
Huh? You read this?
You read this? What's this?
Uh, it's kind of a story theme.
Story theme? Is it written?
Yes, sir.
What's this?
Oh, my God, you already wrote it.
That's amazing.
That's great.
What do you think of each other?
I've never seen you before.
Aro, what is this, an event?
Super teenagers?
Uh, super teenage.
Event? When did you first meet him?
We met when I met you.
We didn't talk, but I...
Longhorns.
No, no, no, no. It was an event.
I saw you. We didn't talk.
I was a super teenager.
I was with Michyopa and Oden.Michyopachan and Oden.
I was thinking, "There's this amazing person who's going to be on the show, too.
I thought, "Wow!
I looked backstage, but there was no one there.
I looked at Michyopa and Aro-chan.
I told her once...
"Isn't Aro-chan big? Like that.
She's got style.
Tampa is.
I'm taller than you and Michyopa.
Aro-chan looks like she's short.
People think you're short.
They'll look at you.
So they're like, "Oh, you're about the same height as her!
She's so stylish. She's so cool.
I'm so happy!
So I was surprised
I was surprised by your style, at first
I'm glad
But I feel the same way.
Really?
I heard you have a pretty face.
People think I'm tiny.
But she's a model.
I thought she was very stylish.
Are we the same?
Yeah.
I'm glad.
And you're a little...
A little flamboyant.It's more like savage.
I mean, the way he talks.
He's very direct.
You're a pleasant person.
I thought he was pleasant?
You're right. He seems so matter-of-fact.
But I'm shy.
That's right.
I didn't see you as shy.
I'm really nervous right now.
You never know.
Shy?
Very shy.
I'm sure you are.
But you'll show it to people you get along with.
If you get to know them really well.
Usually.
What's he like now? How much?
Not yet, because it's the first day we've really talked.
We're just now...
Eight percent.
That's a lot of growth. Eight percent.
Here's the thing.
I've got a lot of talking to do today.
If we get a good price, we'll be done?
I see.
I'm going to ask you a lot of questions, Anna.
I'll ask you questions.
Impressions are over.
Are you done?Are you done?
I'm done with impressions.
I don't know that channel. I know it. You know it? Yeah, I know it. You don't?
Sometimes it comes up as a recommendation. Oh, wow. I've seen it.
I've been wondering why you don't come up with anything often. Why not?
But the guy in charge said he was at one of our events.
Oh, that's right. He was taking Chekkies, Chekkies. He was taking Chekkies.
So he told me at that time, too. Please come out. Oh, really? Yes, that's right. Thank you very much.
The producer really liked it and was very happy with the video. I'm happy.
I'm happy. We are too. It's not often that people from the field come to an event, you know.
That's why I was happy.
What are you talking about? Well then... Cheers.
Cheers.
You're so cute.
You really think so?
I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious about that show.
That's a lie.
It's a lie.
Really? Really?
That's the worst.
No, really.
Really? No, it's not true.
But there are models and idols,
They're really cute.
This is mine. No, no, no, this is mine.
I can't believe it.
I'm happy, but...
I don't lie very much.
I'm not a liar, but I'm flattered?
Really?Really?
She's cute.
I mean, is she your type? I don't know.
I don't know, but I like her face.
Thank you.
Your clothes are cute.
Do you always choose your own clothes?
I always have a few choices from the staff,
But I chose this one because I thought it looked like you-know-who.
It's cute.
Do you pick them yourself?
I went to the store today and put them all together myself.
You brought them all by yourself?
I brought them.
Wow.
That's great.
That's fine.
I want to hear about it.
That's okay.
Enough?
I'd like to hear from Kappa, please.
Let's hear from the cucumbers.
What's that thing that pops up?
I don't know. Why not?
It's cute.
What do you want to be in the future?
I wonder about her.
Future?In the future?
Do you have one?
Do you have a vision for yourself?
I don't really have a vision.
I'm the type of person who lives for the moment. In my work, too.
I'm not that kind of a person.
I don't plan very well.
I don't have much of a plan,
Right now, I'm just doing what I want to do and what I can do as much as I can.
What about 10 years from now?
I can't even think about 10 years from now, can I?
After 10 years? I can think about it.
I think you are very steady,
You are very steady in your planning, and you are making things happen on your own.
You know what I mean.
But I think that's cool.
My life is swimming just like I said it would.
That's amazing.
Does that mean you're thinking things through?
Yes.
What will you be doing in 10 years?
In 10 years, I'll be 25, so 35?
Yeah.
I'll probably be selling mama bags on insta-live when I get there.
Mom bag? Why?
Because I'm married.
I'm married, so if I can have kids before I'm 35 or so, I will,
I want to produce products for moms.
That's great. You're thinking that far ahead.
I've been saying that I want to get married by the time I'm 25.I always said I wanted to get married at 25.
I've been saying it in all kinds of media.
And now I'm right on schedule.
Wow.
I'm getting married at 25, and in 26 or 27, I'll be traveling, which I haven't been able to do before,
I couldn't play as much as I wanted to, so I made friends.
I had 2 years of free time,
I'm going to work as a producer for about 35 years. I like producing.
That's right.
I do my own clothes.
I see. That's great.
I also want to be in magazines.
A magazine?
There is a magazine called Bailey,
It's a mom magazine. There's a magazine for working moms, and I want to be in it.
Wow.
I have a lot of things I want to do, so I made a plan,
It's amazing that you are following your plan.
That's Yagami's light. Oh, my God.
It's all going according to plan.
I guess so.
That's great.
But, you know, it's just words, and if you say them, people around you will move in that direction.
Like in your work. Isn't that right? Do you say what you want to do?
I don't say much, even outwardly.
But I do have things that I want to do.
It's better to say it.
It's better to say it, then it will come true.
What do you want to do? Work.
It can be work or private life.It could be for work, or it could be in your personal life.
Is there a job you'd like to do next?
I want to be in Sasuke.
You'll be out in no time.
Female Sasuke?
Female Sasuke.
That's it, isn't it? The first time, like this, I fell right there.
I want to fall in. I want to get in that muddy water.
You want to go in?
You didn't say that.
Yes, I did. That's what I said.
Don't say it.
That's all I'm saying.
But there's one other thing you haven't said,
What?
I'd like to do some comedy.
That's great.
I'd also like to do some acting,
With a comedian?
I'd like to do that kind of comedy, too.
It'll come true soon.
I mean, if I don't tell them, they won't know about it.
I'm sure of it.
I'm sure, but isn't it difficult for that kind of work to come about spontaneously?
It's difficult.
It would be better to have someone who wants to do it do it.
I see.
You should tell them.
I'll do that.
You will?Will you?
In the future, I don't really see myself doing much, really, 10 years from now.
What will you be doing when you become a grandmother?
But I could be a grandmother.
Yes, if I'm still alive.
If I live.
If I live and become a grandpa, not a grandma.
If I become a grandmother,
I would still like to wear clothes,
And when I become a grandmother, I want to wear something cute.
Are you going to stay in Japan forever?
Overseas?
No?
I want to live slowly.
I don't like greenery now, but I thought I would like it then,
I don't like greenery now, but I thought I would like it then.
I'm sure. I want to be a stylish grandmother in the countryside.
I want to wear Lolita.
Grandmothers.
That's nice.
I'm looking forward to it.
It is.
Let's move on to the next one, shall we?
Next.
Okay, this dog.
Dog.
What? How do you open it?
This is how.
How do you relieve stress?
Stress relief?Stress relief?
It depends on the age, doesn't it?
Hmmm...
I don't know.
I'm a shy person.
I wonder how they relieve stress.
When I was 20 or 21, I used to relieve stress by drinking.
I was drinking a lot.
I drank a lot.
I could drink.
I like to drink, and I like to be in a fun place,
I couldn't go home after work without stopping by one.
I couldn't go home after work without stopping by a bar.
I was working too much,
I thought I would be ruined if I didn't meet someone before I left,
I thought I would be ruined if I didn't meet someone before going home, so I drank a lot of alcohol.
But now, I use it as a stress reliever.
I have a dog now.
Oh, that's right. You have a public dog, right?
Yes, I did. Now that I have a dog in the family,
I don't have to stress anymore.
When I go home, everything goes away.
It's an animal.
That's right. They never betray you.
Animals don't betray you.
They never betray you.
So really, it's not about emotional support,
I don't get stressed out anymore.
I don't know.
Even if I have a bad day, it's all gone when I get home.If I have a bad day, it's all gone when I get home.
Maybe you've found something you want to protect.
Oh, me?
Yeah.
You may be right. This job, too, for sure.
Let's buy good food for them.
Maybe that's why I work.
Stress.
Nothing? Nothing.
I'm not.
How do you do it?
I drink, too.
Drink?
I drink, at home, alone.
Do you eat dinner?
If I let my memory fail me.
Alone?
Yeah.
What?
Alone.
Alone? Why?
I watch TV and record stuff and drink.
What do you drink? Always.
A highball.
Can a highball jog your memory?
Yes, I can.
Really? That's amazing. I definitely have to drink tequila to remember things.
What? Tequila?
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm a little leverette.I'm a little levech.
I can't drink tequila at all.
Can't drink?
But drinking is a bit of a stress reliever,
I'm worried about you because that's what we've been doing.
It's unhealthy.
Seriously unhealthy. My face is swollen.
And I used to party alone.
Isn't your face swollen?
I do, too.
That's no good.
I want something different.
I can't do that before a singing gig,
I'd like to find something different.
I guess.
I want to make something to protect.
You're so busy.
How do you get through it?
I don't know, I don't know.
Do you like it?
Do you enjoy it?
I enjoy it,
But when it's tough, I feel like it's tough work,
But I feel like I have no choice but to do it.
I'm moving forward, and I have time.
I don't have time to play.
I don't have much time to relax.
Anyway, I said, "I'll be back tomorrow,
I'm doing what I have to do.
I remember when I was young,Remind me, because at this young age,
I have memories, you know, from my work,
I could do it at work, but I could do it with my friends,
I wanted to, but I couldn't,
I've been sick, I've been sick.
I've been beaten up since I was young.
I was busiest when I was in high school.
So it was like a bang, you know?
Suddenly I couldn't play anymore,
At that time, I was in the dark every day on Twitter.
Well, that's no longer the case.
What do you do when you have time off?
If I had a day off,
I would play games.
Because, you know, when you're too busy, you can't play games,
I can't play games.
Yes, I can't even play games,
And yet, they don't ask me about games on TV.
I can't play games, thinking that I don't have time to play games,
That's why I want to play games when I have time off.
It's true, I don't want to have episodic talks anymore.
I've been busy with work too,
I don't have days off, so I don't have time to play games,
But I don't have any days off,
I feel like I don't have anything to do,
I asked my manager, "Please give me a day off, even if it's just once a week,
Please give me a day off, even if it's just once a week.
I asked the manager for a day off, even if it's just once a week, so that I can talk about an episode,
I said, "Please give me a day off.
Did you try?Did you say it?
Sure, I'll say it.
I'm in the middle of trying.
I'll say it.
I will.
I'm worried about you. I've been watching you with worry.
Oh, that's so sweet.
Yeah, I just wanted to make sure you were okay.
Which one do you want?
Any of them.
Watermelon, then?
Watermelon.
Oh! You both seem to be heavy fans, what do you value most?
Oh! Nikal, you're the one I think of the most.
We are very fan heavy, if I may say so myself.
Yes, I think we are very fan heavy on Twitter and so on.
I don't know if I'm too much of a fan or if I like my fans too much.
I even got together with a fan at the station and walked her home.
Oh, no!
That's terrible!
He's too kind.
Tell him I'm going home with him.
What?
But I guess that's why he's still so nice to me.
I was closer to the fans.
Isn't it a little too much for you all of a sudden?
That's true.
So maybe it hasn't changed much. We've always been close.
I think it's great.
Because there are people who have been supporting us for a long time, right? Remember them? Their faces?Because there are people who have always supported us, right? Remember them? Faces?
I remember a lot of people from the past.
That's interesting.
It bothers me.
You know, there's this girl who's a fan of mine, and she's like a riaca, and I'll fly over and see what she's up to.
I'll go check it out.
What does he do?
And then I hear they're doing something like idol stuff.
Oh, yeah.
Jealous?
I'd say, "You haven't been to any events lately, so that's what this is about.
And the next time they come to an event, I'll tell them.
But I also look at the stories of those fans.
I do look at them.
I do.
Like the dog they have.
That's true, it's similar. I do look at it.
I do.
I'm not really a fan of all kinds of things.
If it wasn't for them, I wouldn't be able to work as hard as I do.
I wouldn't be doing what I do for a living, and that's why I'm out here like this.
You work hard because your fans are watching you.
If I didn't have any fans.
I'd probably quit my job.
I can't.
No, I can't do it because I wouldn't be doing it without fans.
I wouldn't be able to do it.
Did they ever tell you that you've gone too far away?
Yes, they did.They'll tell you.
When I sold that kitchen.
I was kind of rooting for you at first.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Now that you're all grown up.
You forgot about us, didn't you? It was like...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I've been told that, a lot.
But they said a lot of things about us, so...
I don't know.
I tried not to let them think that, so I made an event where we could meet once a school year.
I made sure that even though I was busy, I never forgot to have an event where we could meet.
I see.
Can we talk in person?
If not before, I'll talk on Twitter or something.
Heh.
That's great. You have a good heart.
But maybe that's because I don't have many friends.
I don't know, you've been so responsive.
I'm not a good friend.
But there are a lot of people who say how cute I look when I take a selfie.
I've had a lot of people tell me how cute I look in my selfies.
I'm so happy that I respond to them.
It makes me happy to get a reaction.
You don't feel lonely.
That's right.
You're close to your fans.
Doesn't it piss you off to be close to them?
Yeah, I do.
So, why did you say that?So, why did you say this?
I'm a huge fan, including cheering for other people.
I'm a huge fan.
Does that piss you off?
No, I'm not pissed off, but I'm too close to my fans.
I get into fights on Twitter.
I mean, I get into fights on Twitter.
When they complain...
I don't know... I'll say something like, "I don't like it.
In a way, I'm just trying to put on a good face when I'm far away.
But I think that's a lie.
It's disrespectful to the fans.
When I was a teenager, I would say it back.
I know.
But there are a lot of girls around the same age as me.
So when I was a teenager...
I had a little bit of bad cheer from the fans.
And they'd get into fights with each other.
And I'd get in between them.
Heh.
Like, "I'm sorry," or "I'm sorry," or "I'm sorry.
I don't know why I have to say I'm sorry.
I don't know why we have to say sorry.
And then there are the fans who remember me.
There's a difference.
And the fans...
They try to understand us
They do all kinds of things to try to understand us.
But the ones who are a little unique are more memorable.
Introduce yourself the same way every time.Or introduce yourself the same way every time.
Or have the same thing every time.
You know, you can't help it.
They're the ones who remember you first.
So if you're on Twitter or something...
If you respond to that...
Why is she always the only one?
Yeah.
Yes, there is.
People say that to me.
It's hard for me.
Even when I didn't like it.
I like them all equally.
I want to be equal, too, but...
I'd like to be equal, but I'd like to give priority to the fans who always come to the show every time.
And people who follow the whole show...
I can't help but remember them.
I do remember some things, but...
I don't know if that's a good thing.
It's her own effort.
That's right, that's right.
Fans marry each other.
Or dating...
It's pretty common.
You mean ano-chan marriages?
Ano-chan marriages and children...
And name the child Anochan's Guchame.
Ano-chan?
I don't think so.
That would be nice.I'm glad to hear that.
I'm glad to hear that.
They're all such fans.
What was the question again?
Well, it's definitely something that we value.
What do you value?
I don't know.
Like I said before.
I don't lie.
I'm the same way.
I never lie.
I'm with you.
You like her a lot.
You do? I don't show it much either.
I don't know.
But it makes you happy, doesn't it? You should respond to her.
Yes, I do.
It's definitely nice.
Thank you.
If you two were going on location again, what would you do? That's the last question I'm going to ask you.
Well, last thing?
Last thing? Do you want to make it last?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Subscribe to our amateur channel!